Diarmuid Brady

Email: diarmuid.b.8612@gmail.com Phone: (087) 3367887 Website: https://nearmo.github.io/personal-website/

Personal Profile

Strong problem solving skills with a keen interest in areas relating to maths, technology, self development and philosophy. I am an active member of DCU's Redbrick society for all things computing and I am an avid reader in my spare time. Passive interest in website creation and have completed a course and competitions on Machine Learning on Kaggle using Pandas.

Languages: Currently learning Python, MySQL and R. Working knowledge of Pandas, Tableau, HTML and CSS. **Tech Stack:** Experience with Git, MySQL Workbench, RStudio.

Education

Dublin City University B.Sc in Data Science

2019 - Present

Currently studying modules including computer programming and databases as well as more math based modules such as calculus and linear maths.

Cnoc Mhuire Secondary School, Granard, Co. Longford Leaving Certificate:

2013-2019 544 Points

Subject	Level	Grade
Mathematics	Higher	H1
Design Communication Graphics	Higher	H1
Physics	Higher	H2
Applied Mathematics	Higher	H2
Accounting	Higher	Н3
French	Higher	H4
English	Higher	H5
Irish	Ordinary	O4

Work Experience

Sales Assistant at Rapture Jack & Jones

Dec 2019 - Jan 2020

- In charge of taking in and packing out large deliveries.
- Maintaining shop and clothing presentations standards
- Assisting customers in the process and purchasing items and serving customers at checkout

Grinds teacher Sept 2019 – Present

- Providing Leaving & Junior Cert grinds to students in the subjects Maths, Technical Graphics and Physics.
- Teaching students the necessary skills to excel in their exams as well as helping them to understand the underlying concepts of the subject.
- Advertising grinds using ad campaigns through Facebook and Instagram page: grinds ic.lc

Camp Leader in Lus Na Gréine Family Resource Centre

June 2019 - July 2019

 Tasked with supervising over 30 children at a time, teaching cooking skills, organising problem solving games and taking charge of other fun learning activities.

General Operative at Dunphy's SuperValu

Jan 2017 - Aug 2018

- In charge of stacking shelves with fresh produce in the Fruit & Veg and Dairy aisles.
- Tasked with providing management with reports and carrying out general cleaning and maintenance cleaning.
- Trusted with opening the shop and locking up at closing hours.

General Operative at Moulding Technology (TY Experience)

Sept 2019 – Oct 2019

- Tasked with operating Injection Moulding Machinery.
- In charge of stripping down and cleaning mould after machine use in order to maintain machine integrity

Awards and Achievements

- Recipient of Cnoc Mhuire award for excellence in leaving cert (544 points).
- Attained full attendance in Leaving Cert year 2018-2019 showcasing excellent punctuality.
- Recipient of student mentor award in leaving cert year for mentoring a small group of 1st year students and helping them settle into life at secondary school.
- Participated in the All-Ireland Junior Maths Competition.
- Longford Minor Division 2 Championship Final Winner with Northern Gaels 2017.

Interests and Hobbies

- Strong interest in Hackathons Attended Hacktoberfest in DCU. Looking to improve coding skills and attend further hackathons in the future.
- Member of Redbrick Society We have discussed areas such as AWS and machine learning and have had guest speakers from different companies talking about the tech stack they use and how they handle data.
- Also actively involved in the Rock Climbing, Philosophy and Chess societies in DCU.
- Hobbies include calisthenics, gaelic football as well as reading books and listening to podcasts on topics such as self development, spirituality and fiction.jku